Mss.B.F865
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letter to Jo[h]n [Fries] Frazer, Jan. 26; 10x7-3/4; Morton, Samuel George, 1799-1851
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning a lecture by Bache.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Feb. 2; 6-1/2x4; Morton, Samuel George, 1799-1851
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Tickets for Bache's lecture.
  - Letter to J[oh]n F[ries] Frazer, Feb. 3; 10x8; Morton, Samuel George, 1799-1851
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Sends tickets for Bache's lecture for the Franklin institute, APS, and the academy.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Feb. 9; 6-3/4x4-1/4; Morton, Samuel George, 1799-1851
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers.) Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Cannot attend Bache's lecture. Refers to Fraley.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Feb. 27; 8x5; Reed, Henry Hope, 1808-1854
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Will not be at the university.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 20; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the telegraph.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 31; 6-1/2x4-1/4; Reed, Henry Hope, 1808-1854
    A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) University business.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, April 4; 8x5-1/4; Meigs, Charles D., (Charles Delucena), 1792-1869
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Thank you note.
  - Letter to John [Fries Frazer], April 15; 6-3/4x4-1/4; Fry, Joseph Reese, d.1865.
    A.L.S. 1p. Enc.wanting (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, April 18; 7x4-1/2; Reed, William B., (William Bradford), 1806-1876
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer?], May 14; 7-3/4x5; Ingersoll, Charles Jared, 1782-1862
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks a favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 25; 8x5-1/4; Brown-Séquard, Ellen (Fletcher)
    A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 26; 8x5; Bache, Evey (Nancy Clarke Fowler)
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, May 27; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Cleveland, Samuel M.
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, June 8; 10x8; Kahler, William
    A.L.S. 3p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning astronomy.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, June 20; 8x4-3/4; Jackson, A. Wendell
    Schenectady, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks a favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, June 25; 8x5; Packard, John H.
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Thanks for favor.
  - Letter to Mrs. [Charlotte Jeffers Cave] Frazer, Aug. 14; 8x5; Bache, Evey (Nancy Clarke Fowler)
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 22; 10x8; Dale, Margaret T.
    Allentown, A.L.S. 2p. Faded. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks a favor.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 24; 8x5; Fraley, F., (Frederick), 1804-1901
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to A.D. Bache.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Sept. 27; 9x7; Packard, F. A.
    A.L.in 3d.P. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning a problem of education.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Sept. 29; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Bache, Evey (Nancy Clarke Fowler)
    Newport, R.I., A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Oct. 21; 8x5; Bache, Evey (Nancy Clarke Fowler)
    Newport, R.I., A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning A.D.Bache. Refers to Fairman Rogers. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Oct. 24; 8x5; Bache, Evey (Nancy Clarke Fowler)
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letter from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to Jo[h]n F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 25; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Kennedy, Alfred L., 1818-
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning lectures at the Franklin institute.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Nov. 6; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Bache, Evey (Nancy Clarke Fowler)
    Newport, R.I., A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazer, Nov. 23; 10x8; Biddle, Edward C., 1808-1893
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Dec. 7; 7-1/2x5; Thompson, A. W.
    A.L.S. 2p. Enc.wanting. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Aid for T.R.Peale. Refers to R.M.Patterson, Henry, and Dunglison.
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazer, Dec. 10; 9-1/2x7-3/4; Fry, Joseph Reese, d.1865.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) University business.
  - Letter to A[lexander] D[allas] Bache, Dec. 10; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Humphreys, A. A., (Andrew Atkinson), 1810-1883
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence..; 1834-1870.) Concerning Elia Lombardini.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Dec. 16; 7-3/4x4-3/4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, undated; 7-3/4x4-3/4; Alexander, J. H. (John Henry), 1812-1867
    Wednesday night. A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 6-3/4x4-1/2; Allen, George, 1808-1876
    Tuesday morning. A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 7x4-1/2 and 5-1/4x5-1/2; Allen, George, 1808-1876
    Thursday morning. A.L.S.with initials. 2p. and (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 8x5-1/4; Allen, George, 1808-1876
    Friday morning. A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870) Friendly letter.
  - Academy of natural sciences of philadelphia, undated; American Philosophical Society
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer., undated; 10x7-3/4; Burrows, J. W.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning heat.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer., undated; 6-1/4x4; Howe, M. A. De Wolfe (Mark Antony De Wolfe), 1809-1895
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer., undated; 8x5; Horsford, Eben Norton, 1818-1893
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Introduces Gould.
    Date late 1830s or early 1840s - H. Miller
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 8x5; Hayes, I. I, (Isaac Israel), 1832-1881
    Monday morning. A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Forwards Bache's publications.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Maas, Jacob
    Monday evening. A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the hiring of a teacher.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], undated; 6-1/4x4; Perot, Elliston
    Tuesday morning. A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks him to observe experiment.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer., undated; 6-1/4x4; Patterson,, Robert M., (Robert Maskell), 1787-1854
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 7x4-1/2; Reed, William B., (William Bradford), 1806-1876
    Monday. A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks to meet him.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], undated; 10-1/2x8; Potter, Alonzo, 1800-1865
    Thursday A.L.S. 2p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the taxing of the academy of natural sciences and the Franklin institute.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 7-3/4x5; Senior, Thomas
    Sunday Evening. A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 7-1/2x5; Torrey, John, 1796-1873
    Wednesday evening. A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Thanks you note.
  - Note to [John Fries] Frazer, undated; 9-1/4x7-1/4; Kane, John K., (John Kintzing), 1795-1858
    Saturday morning. A.N.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Note to [John Fries Frazer], undated; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Monday [ca.1863?]. A.N.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Will breakfast with him. Film 1249.
  - Note to [John Fries] Frazer., undated; 6-1/2x5; Reed, William B., (William Bradford), 1806-1876
    A.N.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning Herschel.
  - Calling card, undated; 2x3; Frazer, John Fries, 1812-1872
    Tuesday. D. 1p.with ms.notes on back. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Film 1249.
  - Resolution concerning John Fries Frazer., undated; 8x5; University of Pennsylvania
    D. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.)
  - Poem, undated
    Undated and unsigned poem.